Welcome, everybody!
欢迎大家！
Welcome to The Tonight Show!
欢迎来到“今夜秀”!
Thank you for watching
感谢收看
Well, guys, it is the last night of Donald Trump's presidency
伙计们，这是唐纳德·特朗普总统任期的最后一个晚上
And, ah…
和……
I don't know what tomorrow's gonna feel like
我不知道明天会怎样
Probably like that moment
大概像那个
when they pull the nasal swab out of your nose
当他们从你鼻子里取出鼻拭子的时刻
At least Trump is leaving on top
至少特朗普从那个位子上离开了
I mean, Washington D.C. has never looked more beautiful
我是说，华盛顿从来没有这么漂亮过
Actually, that has nothing to do with the riots
事实上，这和暴乱没有任何关系
Those are just some of Melania's old Christmas decorations
这些只是梅拉尼娅的一些旧圣诞装饰品
梅拉尼娅·特朗普：前美国第一夫人。
Yep, one more night
是的，又是一个夜晚
For most Americans, it feels like the night of Thanksgiving
对大多数美国人来说，这就像是感恩节之夜
when you're just staring at your aunt and uncle, just thinking
当你一直盯着你的叔叔婶婶，只想着
"Go home"
“回家”
I think everyone is ready for Trump to move on
我想每个人都准备好让特朗普离开了
This afternoon, even the Lincoln Memorial stood up
今天下午，连林肯纪念堂都站了起来
and helped Trump pack
帮特朗普打包行李
He's like," I got it, I got it."
他就像“我懂了，我懂了”
Some people are sad to see Trump go
有些人对特朗普的离去感到难过
Earlier today, the movers shook his hand and said
今天早些时候，搬家工人跟他握手说
"We've never moved so many people out of their offices in four years"
“四年来，我们从来没有让这么多人离开过办公室。”
You put our kids through college
你让我们的孩子读完大学
Thank you
谢谢你！
It was a touching scene at the White House tonight
今晚在白宫发生的一幕非常感人
especially when Trump's for remaining staffers toasted him by raising a glass of bleach
特别是当特朗普剩余员工举起一杯漂白剂向他敬酒时
I thought that was sweet
我觉得这很贴心
Today, all of the White House staffers
今天，所有的白宫工作人员
are signing each other's yearbooks with things like
在彼此的年鉴上签名
"Keep in touch", "Friends for life",
诸如“保持联系” “终身的朋友”
and "I won't tesify against you if you don’t testify against me"
“如果你不指证我，我也不会指证你”之类的
Well, tomorrow morning, Trump's holding a farewell event at Joint Base Andrews
明天早上，特朗普将在安德鲁斯联合基地举行告别活动
特朗普缺席拜登就职典礼，并要求支持者举行送别仪式
I heard that everyone who's invited has to be there by 7:15 a.m.
我听说所有被邀请的人都必须在早上7点15分之前到那里
and they can each bring along five people
他们每人可以带五个人
You know they're having trouble filling seats
你知道他们很难找到人
when they offer everyone a plus-five
当他们给每个人提供了超过五个的座位时
Never heard of a plus-five
从没听说过这事
You can come if you want. You can bring 30 people
如果你愿意，你可以来。你可以带30个人来
But it sounds like a great party
但听起来是个不错的聚会
I mean, the guest have to arrive by 7:15 in the morning
我的意思是，客人必须在早上7:15之前到达
on a Wednesday in the middle of January during a pandemic
在1月中旬疫情期间的星期三
Even Craigslist actors were like, "Pass"
就连Craigslist（美国最火的分类网站）上的演员都说“算了”
And this is true, the guest list is so thin
这是真的，来宾名单太薄了
even Anthony Scaramucci got invite
就连安东尼·斯卡拉穆奇也收到了邀请
安东尼·斯卡拉穆奇：前白宫幕僚，仅上任10天即被解雇。
You know your party is struggling
你知道你的政党正在挣扎
when it's half family and half staff you fired four years ago
当它是你四年前解雇的半个家庭中的半个员工时
But today, Trump released a pre-recorded farewell address
但今天，特朗普发布了事先录制好的在白宫的告别演说
from the White House, and here are some of the highlights
下面是一些重点报道
Now as I prepare to hand power over to a new administration
现在我正准备将权力移交给新一届政府
at noon on Wednesday
在星期三中午
I want you to know that the movement we started is only just beginning
我想让你们知道，我们的乐章才刚刚开始
We did what we came here to do
我们做了我们来这里应该做的事
and so much more
并且做了不少分外的事情
The world respects us again
所有人敬佩我们的作为
Please don't lose that respect
请不要失去这种敬佩感
Yeah
是的
Trump said, "We did what we came here to do,"
特朗普说，“我们做了我们来这里应该要做的事，”
It’s true, I remember his big campaign promise was,
是真的，我记得他的竞选承诺是，
"Build part of a wall and pay for it ourselves"
自己掏腰包建造隔离墙的一部分
Yep, Trump also said "The world respects us again,"
没错，特朗普还说“世界再次敬佩我们，”
When he heard that, Vladimir Putin was like
当他听到这个消息的时候，弗拉基米尔·普京说
"Yes, yes, is always good to end with joke."
“是的，以笑话结尾总是好事。”
"Classic, Buddy."
“经典，弟”
But today wasn't all bad
但今天也不全是坏事
There was actually some nice news for Trump
对特朗普来说，还有一些好消息
Listen to this
听听这个
President Trump's youngest daughter has a big announcement
特朗普总统的小女儿有一件大事要宣布
蒂芙尼·特朗普订婚
Tiffany Trump is getting married
蒂芙尼·特朗普要结婚了
The 27-year-old took to Instagram to announce her happy news
27岁的她在Instagram上宣布了自己的喜讯
Trump was so sweet
特朗普太贴心了
He was like, "This week isn't about you, Tiffany!"
他说"这周的主角不是你，蒂芙尼"
Asked what she's most excited for
问她最兴奋的事是什么
Tiffany was like, "Changing last names."
蒂芙尼说"改姓"
Some entertainment news
还有一些娱乐新闻
Last night was an all-new episode of The Bachelor
昨晚是新的一期《单身汉》
and Serena had a one-on-one date with Matt
瑟琳娜和马特单独约会了
And the date was going well until an unexpected visitor showed up
约会进行得很顺利，直到一个不速之客出现
Watch this
看这个
The feelings that I'm already having for you
我对你已经有感觉了
like, throughout this experience is like
在整个这段经历中就像
they're real
他们是真实的
All that was missing was a graphic that said
只是缺了张图，上面写着
"Donkey, age 7, social media influencer"
“毛驴，7岁，社交媒体影响者”
Yep, now along with herpes
是啊，现在又加上疱疹病毒了
"The Bachelor" has to worry about foot-and-mouth disease
“单身汉”不得不担心口蹄疫的问题了
Hey, check this out
嘿，看看这个
I saw that Nissan has designed a new concept van
我看到尼桑设计了一款新的概念车
intended to serve as a mobile office for remote workers
旨在为远程工作人员提供移动办公室
Take a look at this
看看这个
Yeah, and this is cool
是的，这很酷
It comes with a bumper sticker that says
保险杠贴纸上写着
"I didn’t get custody"
我没有得到保护
Yep, Nissan will release the car right after everyone is vaccinated
没错，等每个人都接种完疫苗，回到办公室后
and returns to the office
尼桑就会把车投放市场
We have a great show
我们的节目很精彩
Give it up for The Roots everybody
掌声送给扎根合唱团